In this course, our goal is to learn the fundamental elements of image processing. Among the various subfields of image processing and computer vision, this class will focus on the basics of Autoencoder structures and image generation. Rather than delving deeply into complex mathematical equations, we will introduce key ideas, architectural concepts, and workflows.

패턴인식, 확률및및통계, 선형대수학, 인공지능개론

In the early semester, our course will initially concentrate on explaining Convolutional modules to help students understand the underlying structures. In the mid to later semester, the focus will shift towards deep learning architectures, covering essential concepts and structures in the context of image processing and generation.

We aim to learn basic knowledge of Image processing.We aim to learn basic knowledge of Image generation.