In this course, we will study integral and differential calculus.First, we will study single variable differentiation and its applications.Second, we will study single variable integration and its applications.Further, we will also study series and Taylor series expansion.Finally, we will study multivariable differential calculus including gradient, partial derivative and etc.This is a Davinci learning lecture.

+ We will study theoretical understanding of differential and integral.+ We will study how to formulate mathematical problems from the real problems.

+ Students cultivate basic knowledge of calculus as a foundation of mathematics.+ Students can analyze and solve various calculus problems.