You will all remember solving two simultaneous equations for two unknowns in high school. Linear algebra is the elegant structure that arises when you generalize this to many equations in many unknowns. We will find such algebra problems (involving numbers and matrices) can be beautifully described by geometry (involving planes and angles).Linear algebra is a branch of mathematics that studies systems of linear equations and the properties of matrices. The concepts of linear algebra are extremely useful in artificial intelligence and computer engineering.In this course will cover many linear algebra topics including, but not limited to, systems of linear equations, matrices, determinants, Cramer’s rule, vectors, vector spaces, basis and dimension, linear transformations, eigenvalues, eigenvectors, and quadratic forms.

This course is designed to cultivate problem-solving techniques using linear algebra. More specifically, students will learn the theory and practice of solving and understanding any linear system you could come across, including learning some methods of rigorous proof.

Students will learn the following themes through the course:- Solving systems with linear equations,- Handling matrices and vectors,- Concepts of linear independence, spanning, spaces, and rank,- Eigen decompositions and their applications