The main objective of the class is to help students understand the mathematical foundation for machine learning and its applications in the computer vision domain. Computer Vision is one of the major fields in computer science and its potential application is increasingly extended. Students will learn mathematical techniques that will serve as foundations to understand the theoretical aspect of machine learning and students are expected to understand and implement some applications of the computer vision techniques. Note that it is required to prepare knowledge about Linear Algebra, Numerical Analysis, and Python Programming.The main objective of the class is to help students understand the mathematical foundation for machine learning and its applications in the computer vision domain. Computer Vision is one of the major fields in computer science and its potential application is increasingly extended. Students will learn mathematical techniques that will serve as foundations to understand the theoretical aspect of machine learning and students are expected to understand and implement some applications of the computer vision techniques. Note that it is required to prepare knowledge about Linear Algebra, Numerical Analysis, and Python Programming.	

- This course aims to improve students' mathematical skills that include linear algebra, numerical analysis and optimisation.- This course aims to develop students' python programming skills.- This course aims to help students understand the machine learning and computer vision fields.- This course aims for students to develop these implementation skills for machine learning and computer vision techniques.- This course aims to help students develop skills related to the open source development framework

- Python programming- Linear algebra- Numerical Analysis- Machine Learning- Image Processing- Computer Vision- collaborative software development tools such as git- machine learning libraries developed in the open source platform