-Learn how to use Python for data analysis  (advance level) -Learn how to use following libraries:   Pandas   Numpy  Scikit-LearnPlease note that this course is an advance level course for students from Dept of AI. For all other students, you will be asked to leave if you fail the screening exam on Day1. For the screening exam, you will be asked to implement 'advanced level python coding'  - Before you plan to take this course you should be able to do including , but not limited to 1. Should know all different kinds of data structures in python (set, lisg, tuple, dictionary....) 2. Should be able to implement your own functions with advanced skills, passing functions as argument, anonymous functions 3. Have taken linear algebra, probability theory.

Python Programming; Data Structure; Algorithms

1. Learn how to perform data preprocessing and data analysis.2. Learn how to use open-source libraries for data analysis.3. Learn how to conduct own research with data analysis. (will be learning Recommender Systems in depth)

Students will be able to conduct their own research with data analysis. Specifically, we focus on data preprocessing for machine learning, conduct ML-based research using ML-libraries and modify existing classes, handle large scale datasets.