This course provides basic probability theory, random process, and related topics for machine learning and other applications.	

Calculus, Linear Algebra

This course aims to understand the basic concept of probability and random process for AI researchers and engineers.

We will study the following concepts in the class.- Set Theory, Probability- Bayes’ Rule, Independence- Random Variable (Discrete, Multiple, Continuous)- Central Limit Theorem- Gaussian Random Variable- Random Vectors- Random Process- Gaussian Process- Poisson Process- Wiener Process- Markov Process