\This course will introduce several search and optimization algorithms to build an intelligent AI agent. In this course, students will learn and practice about several search algorithms. Specific topics include A* algorithm, tree-based search, constraint satisfaction algorithm, and/or Markov decision process.이 강의에서는 지능형 AI 에이전트를 구축하기 위한 몇 가지 탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘을 소개합니다. 학생여러분은 여러 검색 알고리즘에 대해서 배우고 연습하게 됩니다. 예를 들어, A* 알고리즘, 트리 기반 탐색, 제약 조건 만족 알고리즘, 마르코프 의사 결정 프로세스 등을 배우게 됩니다.

Basic Programming (기초프로그래밍), Algorithm(알고리즘), AI Mathematics(인공지능수학)

1. Students will be able to tell fundamental concepts behind various search algorithms.각종 탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘의 기초와 아이디어에 대해서 이해한다.2. Students will be able to write a creative code for a search algorithm.각종 탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘을 작성하는 방법에 대해 연습한다.3. Students will be able to communicate about how to implement a specific search algorithm.각종 탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘을 구현하는 방법에 대해 소통할 수 있다.4. Students will be able to distinguish possible ethical issues when using a search algorithm.각종 탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘을 적용할 때 발생할 수 있는 윤리적 문제에 대해 구별할 수 있다.

At the end of this course, the student will be able to do the following:1. Understand how a search algorithm works탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘이 돌아가는 방법에 대한 이해2. Write a program using a search algorithm탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘을 작성하는 방법에 대한 이해와 실행 능력3. Discuss about the difference between search algorithms여러 탐색 및 최적화 알고리즘 사이의 차이에 대한 이해