In this course, we will understand and learn how to develop programs to solve various problems in the computer field using Java, an object-oriented programming language.To this end, the main concepts of object-oriented language such as an object, inheritance, polymorphism, and the grammar of Java are studied.Through this, various problems can be solved using an object-oriented language.

- Understand programming development methods for solving various problems using Java, an object-oriented programming language, and use them to solve the problems.

- Understand the programming development environment and be able to use development tools.- Java code to solve a given problem can be written using an object-oriented language.