This course introduces the fundamental knowledge of robotics, such as kinematics, inverse kinematics, motion planning, control theory, and more. Additionally, it explores practical approaches to controlling real robots based on the acquired knowledge. The goal is to manipulate objects using a robotic arm.* This course will not cover dynamics such as equations of motion.* The main objective of this course is to learn software skills for controlling a hardware system. So, students will simultaneously study both hardware and software, and the course will involve a challenging journey with coding assignments, projects, and exams.

Linear Algebra(선형대수학), Algorithm(알고리즘), Data Structure(자료구조), Python(기초프로그래밍)

1. Kinematics2. Inverse Kinematics,3. Planning Algorithms4. PID control5. Robotic Grasping

Students can understand the basic principles of how robots operate and acquire the ability to control them.